人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   小萌
时间轴：小萌        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十一集
汉堡够热吗
Will the burger be hot enough?
能杀死致命细菌吗
Hot enough to kill the deadly bacteria?
要是不够热的话我就要关掉你这家店
Or is it so cool that I will shut you down?
163  164[华氏度]
One sixty-three, one sixty-four...
One sixty-five.
-肉饼够热  是安全的  -该死
- Hot patty. It's safe. - Damn it!
-太好啦  -太好啦
- Yay! - Yay!
A级碎牛肉
Grade-A ground beef.
ground beef 意为"绞碎的牛肉"
但其中的ground一词也有"地面"的意思
-就是我们扔到地上过的肉  -露易丝
- Meaning we dropped it on the ground. - Louise.
-你查完了没  雨果  -差不多了
- Are we done here, Hugo? - Almost.
还有一件小事
There's just the little matter
你的洗手检定书
of your handwashing certification.
怎么没挂在显眼的地方
I don't see it prominently displayed anywhere.
得了  没人洗个手还得需要检定
Come on, nobody needs to be certified in handwashing.
没错  别摸我的手  政府人员
Yeah! Hands off my hands, government!
如果你还想营业
If you wish to remain open,
你就得参加一个为期一天的学习班
you will attend a one day seminar
学习正确的32步洗手程序
exploring the 32 steps of proper hand sanitation.
我才不去上那个学习班
I'm not taking that seminar.
你看完这个视频介绍就不会这么说了
Not before you watch the introductory DVD, you're not.
得了  雨果
Come on, Hugo.
这是给你评的C级检定书
And here's your "C" rating
卫生部门  违规通知
在你毕业之前它会一直贴在餐厅的窗户上
which will remain in your window until you graduate.
食品质检部门  违规通知
该厨师的手又脏又臭
什么  雨果  你真是个烂人
What?! Hugo, you're an awful man.
错了  鲍勃
Uh, wrong, Bob.
我是守法的人
I'm a "Lawful" man.
沙拉三明治人
Falafel man.
除蒂娜外  其他几人说的都互相押韵
-华夫饼人 -鸡蛋饼人
- Waffle man. - Omelettes.
我跟上了吗
Am I doing it right?
咱们得走了  雨果
We should get going, Hugo.
你们下一个打算去给谁捣乱
Who're you going to harass next, guys?
鲍勃  如果你真想知道
Well, Bob, if you must know,
也许你已经听说了  我们的小镇现在
perhaps you've heard our town is now home
有一个非常恶心的裸体海滩
to a disgusting nude beach?
据报道  那里的商贩卖食物的时候
There've been reports of vendors there serving food
都裸  裸着身子
while n-n... naked.
圣经里的商贩就是这样卖食物的
That's how the vendors served food in the Bible.
-别把宗教扯进来  -抱歉
- Don't drag religion into this. - Sorry.
再见啦  鲍勃
So long, Bob.
去取得检定书
Get certified
否则C代表的将是餐馆倒闭
or that "C" will stand for "Closed."
倒闭的英文单词的第一个字母是"C"
你好  我是安德烈・罗佑
Hi. I'm Andre Royo.
我在广受好评的电视剧《火线》中
I played Bubbles
扮演包博思一角
on the critically acclaimed series The Wire.
今天我要说的是另外一种泡沫
Today I'm here to talk about a different kind of bubbles.
bubbles 也有泡沫的意思
肥皂泡沫
Soap bubbles.
记住  在你洗手时
Remember, when washing your hands,
要数上一千遍
do it for the time it takes to count to a thousand.
一  二  三  四
One... two... three... four...
鲍鲍  咱俩什么时候去一趟
Bobby, when are you and me
雨果提过的那个裸体沙滩
gonna go to that nude beach that Hugo was talking about?
去那儿的都是发了福
Ugh. Nude beaches are full of overweight,
上了年纪的胖子
out-of-shape old bodies and I don't want to go there
我可不想去提醒自己我和他们一模一样
and realize I look exactly like that.
我跟你去  老妈
I'll go with you, Mom.
"母女坦诚相见"日  有意思
Mother-daughter nudity day. Fun!
我很肯定那里不许小孩进入
I'm pretty sure it's no kids allowed.
不许小孩进入
No kids allowed?
来看看  告诉我你看到了什么
Look through here and tell me what you see.
有个悬崖
It's a cliff.
该我了
My turn!
的确是个悬崖  没错
That's a cliff, all right.
蒂娜  你做到了
Tina, you nailed it!
不  那是个能看到裸体沙滩全貌的悬崖
No, it's a cliff that overlooks the nude beach.
如果我们想办法爬上去
And if we figure out how to get up there,
我们就可以卖门票了  看裸体的门票
we could sell tours... nudity tours...
卖给那些少年们
to teenage boys.
相当于在户外看A片
It's like the Internet, but outside.
太好了
Yes!
拜托
Hey, whoa, God!
我们都还没到裸体海滩呢
We're not even at the nude beach yet, you.
看来我的胸部没领会到这一点
Guess my boobs didn't get the memo.
可穿可不穿海滩  18岁以下不得进入
就像在巴黎一样
It's like we're in Paris.
-我太喜欢了  -我知道
- I love it. - I know.
这就是生活啊  来吧
C'est la vie. Let's go! Whoo!
不得擅自进入  违者将被起诉
此处不通往海滩
使劲砍  加把劲  伙计们
Keep hacking! Come on, guys,
我们会成为向往裸体的刘易斯与克拉克
we're gonna be the Lewis and Clark of nudism!
刘易斯与克拉克远征军
美国国内首次横越大陆西抵太平洋沿岸的往返考察活动
那我就是萨卡加维亚
I'll be the Sacajawea.
曾随克拉克和刘易斯的西征探险队探险
向往小鸡鸡的
Of sacks!
真是太有趣了
This is fun!
你都已经脱掉底裤了
You already took your bottoms off!
那是个什么形状
Whoa, whoa! What kind of shape is that?
我说不好  本来想剃个三角形
I don't know, it started out to be a triangle,
但后来我被迫自己动手  结果怎么说呢
but then I had to do it myself, and then, I don't know...
可以认为是一朵花
it's like a flower or something.
看那个打鼓的帅哥
Check out the hot guys in the drum circle.
你好
Hi.
那人像是  天哪
Hey, that looks like... Oh, my God!
鲍鲍  你绝对不会相信
Bobby, you're not gonna believe this.
他去裸体沙滩了
He was at the nude beach!
-等等  你说的是谁  -雨果
- Wait, who was there? - Hugo!
是的  他是去取缔那个地方的
Yeah, he was trying to shut the place down.
不  现在他是他们中的一员了
No, he's one of them now.
-什么的一员  -裸体主义者  裸者
- One of what? - A nudist! Nudie!
他在海浪中演奏  跳着舞
He was playing in the waves. Dancing around.
看起来就像
He looked like, ah...
《珍爱》MV里的麦当娜一样
Madonna in the "Cherish" video.
不可能吧
Th-that's not possible.
他说他休了假去当裸者
He said he took a leave of absence to be nude.
那么  雨果不再是我们的卫生检查员了
So... Hugo's not our health inspector anymore?
你知道这意味着什么吗
Do you know what this means?
我们自由了
We're free!
不再有检查员出其不意来检查了
No more surprise inspections! Ha, ha!
不再有愚蠢的违规通知了
No more stupid violations!
我不用再去上洗手课了
And I am not going to the handwashing class!
真脏
Filth!
我洗手的
I wash my hands.
真不敢相信
Unbelievable.
卫生检查员雨果居然是个裸体主义者
Hugo the health inspector is a nudist!
我知道  你能相信吗
I know, can you believe it?
我和格雷琴在沙滩上远远地就发现了他
Gretchen and I spotted him from across the sands...
呼出污气
Out with the bad air,
吸入裸气
in with the nude air.
别害羞  琳达
Don't be embarrassed, Linda.
是的  我们曾经是情侣
Yes, we were once an item,
没错  我们从来没有彼此赤裸相见过
and true, we never saw each other nude back then...
很可惜
unfortunately...
可亡羊补牢  为时不晚嘛
but better late than never.
怎么回事  你不是来取缔这个地方的吗
What happened? I thought you were gonna shut this place down.
你是说我的调查吗
Oh, my investigation?
这么说吧  在这次调查中
Let's just say what I uncovered in that investigation
我找到了自己的灵魂
was my very own soul.
以前的雨果看到这个人
The old Hugo would have seen this man
会认为他是完全就是个有害健康的因子
as a health hazard, pure and simple.
新的雨果看到的就只是一个人
The new Hugo sees only a man.
一个裸着身子卖蛋糕的人
A nude man selling blondies.
给我三个  谢谢
Three blondies, please.
你从哪变出的钱
Whoa, wai... Wha... Where'd you pull that from?
-我的腰包  -你的腰包在哪
- My fanny pack. - Where's your fanny pack?
在那儿呀
There it is.
这倒是讲得通
Well, it kind of makes sense.
这人浑身肥肉
I mean, the guy was wound so tight
就像个桶状的定时炸弹
he was like a tubby little time bomb.
天线宝宝定时炸弹
Teletubby time bomb.
过来  孩子们  我有个好消息要宣布
Kids! Come in here! I have amazing news.
不能等等再说吗  我们累死了
Can't it wait? We're tired.
还痒痒得要死
And rashy.
你们去哪了
Where were you?
去开辟通往裸体海滩的道路了
Bushwacking a trail to the nude overlook.
老爸  在你开口前
Dad, before you say anything,
要知道这笔生意会让我们发大财
know that we're gonna come out of this deal stinkin' rich!
到时候你和老妈就不必露宿街头了
And we're gonna put a roof over you and Ma.
祝你们好运  给我钱我都不会去看的
Well, good luck. I'd pay not to have to look at those people.
老爸  回到刚才你说的
Hey, Dad, whoa, whoa, whoa, rewind.
我想听听你的好消息
I'd like to hear your amazing news.
大家听好了  雨果不再是卫生检查员了
Everyone, Hugo is not a health inspector anymore.
他现在是一个裸体主义者
He's a nudist!
罗恩  我想我知道你来此的目的
Ron! I think I know why you're here.
你说吧  我可以假装还不知道
Go ahead, I'll pretend I haven't heard.
没错
It's true.
雨果请假了
Hugo has taken a leave of absence.
我们非常想念他并期待他早日回归
We miss him terribly and hope for his speedy return.
最好是
Ha-ha! Right.
好了
All right, well,
为你们介绍接替雨果的人
I'd like you to meet Hugo's replacement.
你们好  我是汤米・贾龙达  幸会
Hey, hello, Tommy Jaronda. Pleasure to meet you.
你好  那么  你就是新雨果吗
Hi. Uh... what, you're the new Hugo?
雨果是无可替代的
Well, there's only one Hugo.
既然我人在这儿了  那就开始吧
Yeah, well, I'm here, so let's get into it.
贾龙达质检员
Oh, um... listen, Inspector, uh, Jaronda,
我知道你是在尽份内之责
I know you're just doing your job,
但是我们前两天才被检查过  所以
but we got inspected two days ago, so...
没关系  鲍勃
Yeah, yeah, it's cool, Bob.
这样吧  叫我汤米好了
Yeah, yeah, you know what? Call me Tommy.
好吧  汤米
Okay, Tommy.
好的
All right.
都是些千篇一律的违规控诉嘛
I'm seeing a lot of tickytacky fouls here.
不是吧  他还逼你去参加洗手学习班吗
What, he made you go to a handwashing seminar?
放什么屁呢
That's some major B.S.
我为我的措辞道歉  孩子们  你们好
Pardon my language, kids. How are you? Hello.
我们完全不介意
No sweat off our ass.
是啊  那个雨果是跟我们杠上了
Yeah, that Hugo, he kind of had it out for us.
我最受不了那种质检员了
Ugh. I-I can't stand inspectors like that.
搞得我们遭人唾弃
You know? Makes us look like turds.
"遭人唾弃的人都是自作自受"
"No one can make you look like a turd
埃莉诺・罗斯福说的[美国前第一夫人]
without your permission." Eleanor Roosevelt.
这孩子真机灵  有意思  有意思
Ha! This kid's a trip! Funny stuff, funny stuff.
你知道吗  我其实
You know what? I'm actually, uh...
饿得不行了  你呢  罗恩
I'm starving. You hungry, Ron-Ton?
你是想吃这家店的汉堡吗
You mean eat one of Bob's burgers?
-雨果是绝对不会  -来吧  罗恩
- Hugo would never... - Oh, come on, Ron.
这家伙...  他是有多高啊
This guy... How tall is this guy?
-他很高  -高个...高个斜塔
- He's pretty tall. - The leaning tower of ta... of tall guy.
给点面子  来吧
You're giving me a hard time, come here.
鲍勃  能给我们烤两个汉堡吗
Hey, Bob, can you grill us up a couple?
这是检查的一个流程吗
Um... is this part of the inspection?
可以这么说吧  我把它叫做以身试法
Uh, yeah, something I like to call the mouth inspection.
好吧
Okay.
太棒了
Whoa! This is incredible!
这可是我第一次从质检员口中
Wow, first time I ever got a compliment
受到好评
from a health inspector.
问你个问题  鲍勃  你喜欢摇滚吗
Bob, question: You like rock?
喜欢
Um, yeah.
我喜欢摇滚音乐
I like rock... music.
你是这个意思吧
Is that what you're talking about?
-是的  -好吧
- Yes. - Okay.
你知道吗  我每晚都在
You know, I play almost every night
"手枪酒吧"演出
over at Pistol McSwish's Basketball and Brew.
你应该过来听听
You should come by.
太  太好了  我一定去
Th-That'd be great. Absolutely.
你的汉堡满足了我的味觉
What your burger did to my mouth,
我会用我的音乐满足你的听觉
my music is gonna do to your ears.
太好了
That's great...
-来  来  -好的  好的
- Come here, come here. - All right, all right.
-过来嘛  -你要干嘛
- Get out of here, man. - What are you doing?
-来嘛  -被你逮到了
- Yeah, come here. - Oh. You got me.
你打我了吗  我要打回去
What, you punching me? I'm punching you back.
我觉得老爸和那人已经到二垒了
I think Dad just got to second base with that guy.
老弟  你这周周末做什么
What are you doing this weekend, brother?
我想去裸体海滩
I would like to visit the nude beach
看裸体
and see the naked people.
机不可失失不再来  对吧  老姐
You only live once, right, my sister?
你没听说吗
Haven't you heard?
小孩禁止去裸体海滩
Kids aren't allowed on the nude beach.
不
No!
是不是很不公平
Unfair, isn't it?
如果我说我能让你们去裸体海滩呢
Well, what if I told you that you could see the nude beach?
只需要交很低的入场费
All the dingles... Ooh.
毛发  菊花
All the dongles... Ahh.
应有尽有
All for one low price.
我想看菊花
I want to see the dongles!
必须的  还有带"巧克力豆"的咪咪
Hell, yeah! Cocoa-buttered boobies!
想去悬崖看裸体的人在这儿签名
Sign up here to see the buff from the bluff!
别害羞  那些裸体可一点都不害羞
Don't be shy... they certainly aren't.
你好  露易丝
Hello, Louise.
达瑞尔  你也有兴趣吗
Darryl, you interested?
我还以为你是宅男呢
You strike me as more of an indoor nerd.
我是有兴趣
I am interested,
但不是作为顾客
but not as a customer...
而是作为你们团队的核心成员
as a key member of your team.
我是来入股的
For a piece of the action?
是这样啊
Oh-ho-ho, is that so?
是的
It is so.
如果你们是从悬崖上看裸体
If you're nudie watching from the top of a bluff,
我这儿有能让你们利润翻倍的东西
I've got something that'll double your money.
这堪称是专为看咪咪而造的哈勃望远镜
Basically, this is the Hubble for boobies.
我已经用它欣赏对街的邻居
I've seen my neighbor across the street
换内衣系腰带不下一百次了
put her bra and girdle on hundreds of times.
不是只有老人家才系腰带吗
Aren't girdles for old people?
是啊  她就是老人家
They are. And she is.
很好
Nice.
我为什么都是我们推
How come we're doing all the lugging?
就你话最多
You're also doing all the yapping.
裸体
Nudes, ho!
明天起钞票就会源源不断地向我们涌来啦
Starting tomorrow, we're gonna be flush with ass-cash.
你干嘛  老爹
Whatcha doin', Pops?
要去外面喝一杯吗
Hitting the streets for some hooch?
不  他要去"手枪酒吧"
No, he's off to Pistol McSwish's
看那个新来的质检员的演出
to see the new health inspector play his rock.
我必须去
I have to go.
这个人要站在我们这边才行
We want to keep this guy on our side.
汤米  我正打算去看...
Tommy! I was just heading out to catch your set...
鲍勃  你肯定不信
Bob! You're never gonna believe it!
那个叫"手枪酒吧"的白痴老板
That idiot who owns Pistol McSwish's
跟我说我不能在那儿演出了
told me I can't play there anymore!
什么  为什么
- What? How come? '- Cause he don't know nothin'
因为他根本不懂摇滚乐  这就是原因
about good rock, that's how come.
等等  有了  我可以在这儿唱啊
Wait... Hey, I could play here.
这儿
Here?
-啥  -没错
- Uh, what? - Yeah.
-不行  -对  不行
- Nah. - Yeah, no.
这的收音效果不...
The acoustics in here are not...
不  这儿的收音效果好得很
No. The acoustics in here are great.
对  对  对  这儿的音效很不错
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, sounds good in here.
-拍手  我爱拍手  -回音  回音
- Oh, clapping. Clapping's fun. - Echo. Echo.
-够了  够了  -回音  回音
- Stop. Stop. - Echo. Echo.
吉恩  够了  吉恩
Gene, stop. Gene.
鉴定完毕  我去拿我的放大器
Oh, it's done. I'm grabbing my amp.
也许没那么糟呢
Maybe it won't be so bad.
*我是个有绝技的坏男人*
*I'm a bad man with a master plan*
*姑娘们都叫我特克斯*
*And the ladies call me Tex*
*她们都心知肚明*
*And the one thing all the ladies know is*
*我擅长*
*I'm good at having...*
*做爱爱爱爱爱爱爱*
*Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex*
*我没脱上衣  没关系*
*I leave my shirt on, that's okay*
*别让我难为情  宝贝儿*
*Don't make me feel self-conscious, babe*
*做爱爱爱爱爱爱爱  完事儿请说爽*
*Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, when you're done, say that was fun*
我们也许会生个儿子
*We might've made a little son*
*我是做爱高手  你是做爱新手*
*I'm good at sex, you're bad at sex*
*I'm good at sex, you're bad at sex, I'm good at sex...*
天哪
Oh, my God.
汤米的演出太可怕了
Tommy's music is terrible.
他把客人都吓跑了
He's driving out all the customers.
你居然跟他说可以在这儿唱一个星期
You told him he could play here all week?
我好像没说
I don't think I did.
我说了  但这总比对付雨果强吧
I did. But this is still way better than dealing with Hugo.
你得跟他说说
You got to say something.
那首歌是叫"老妓女"么  这你也能忍
What about that song, "Elderly Prostitute"?
老妓女
Elderly prostitute
Elderly prostitute...
好吧  我去跟他说
All right, I'll say something.
你们觉得如何  喜欢我的音乐吗
So, what'd you guys think? Did you like my rock?
汤米  酷  酷毙了
Tommy, that, uh... rocked.
那是当然  琳达  你觉得呢
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Linda, what'd you think?
作为女士你能懂吗
Ha! Did it speak to you as a lady?
-说实话  -简直让我神魂颠倒了
- Now be honest. - It screamed in my face as a lady.
老妈可喜欢了  卖张CD给她吧
Oh, Mom loved it. Sell her a CD.
没问题
Done.
听着  汤米
Yeah, listen, Tommy,
能和你说两句吗
can I talk to you about something I...
走  去后台说  走吧
Come on, let's go backstage. Let's go.
什么  好吧
What? Oh. Okay.
老哥
WhooMan.
这就是那些不懂摇滚的人不能领会的地方
What people don't know about rock,
摇滚其实是一种很耗体力的  经历
it's a very physical...experience, you know?
可以说是一种运动
It's-it's very athletic.
你唱歌的时候是挺活跃的
You're moving around a lot.
是吧  是吧  你发现了
Yeah, yeah. You noticed that.
好像有点儿太活跃了
It's almost like you moved around too much.
是的  对我的评论可谓五花八门
Yeah, I've gotten all kinds of comments, you know...
"你太活跃了"
"You move around a lot,"
"你好像很辛苦"
"You seem to be having a hard time."
这点我多少能看出来
Yeah, I can see that one, a little bit.
-"你犯不着那样跳来跳去"  -没错
- "You're jumping around for no reason." - Right.
"你的鱼泡眼丑爆了  真扫兴"
"You know, your eyes are bulging weird. It's off-putting,"
唧唧歪歪  他们当初也这么说皇后乐队
this and that... but that's what they said about Queen.
是吗  也这么说了
Yeah. Did they?
摇滚圈就是这样
Uh, in rock in general.
汤米  你知道吗
Hey, uh, Tommy, uh... you know,
我们餐馆是主打家庭温馨风格
our place is sort of a family restaurant and...
你的一些歌实在有点难登大雅之堂
some of your songs are a little risque.
所以我觉得  是不是可以...
So I was thinking, maybe don't...
等等  等一下
Wait. Hold on a second.
我怕一会儿给忘了  给你看样东西
Before I forget, I got a little something here for you...
你餐馆的检定文件
it's your inspection file.
上面什么也没写啊
There's nothing on here.
那就对了  记录一笔勾销  不用谢我
That's right! Clean slate. You're welcome.
真的吗
Wow. Really?
是啊  行了  什么都不用说了
Yeah, come on, shut up.
真谢谢你了  汤米
Well, thanks, Tommy.
我的老兄
Oh, man.
我现在还感觉浑身充满魔力呢
I still got all that mojo flowing through me.
我得去释放释放
You know, I-I got to get it out.
我要开着这台面包车去海滩
I'm gonna take this van to the beach
放松放松  你要来吗
and peel off some burnies. You want to come?
怎  怎么放松
Um... what's a... wh-what's a burny?
我快要吐了
Ah! Ah, I'm gonna throw up!
我要回家
I want to go home!
回什么家  多有意思啊
What? This is fun!
我不想放松了
Oh, no more burnies!
好啦 大家排好队
All right, people, line up!
大家可以看到
You'll see we have many noteworthy specimens
今天海滩上有许多值得一看的样品
on the beach today.
只要一美元就可以近距离观赏
Only a dollar to get a closer look at the action.
过来吧
Step right up!
透过望远镜  看好多咪咪
Look through this tube, see some boob.
再掏点票票  瞅好多"弟弟"
Give me the green, see some peen.
真恶心
Hey, this is gross.
我们大老远来  就是看老头老太的吗
We came all this way to see old people?
真恶
Ew! Nasty!
你耍我们呢
You tricked us.
把钱还给我
I want my money back.
等等啊  小伙们
Whoa-whoa, wait, whoa-ho-ho, you guys,
你们心态根本没摆正
you're looking at this the wrong way.
想看完美胴体是吗
You want to see nice bodies?!
去看《花花公子》啊
Get a magazine!
这可是三次元真人好吗
This is real, people!
看看那个人  那是什么
Check out that guy. What is that?
是雀斑还是胎记
Is that a liver spot? Is that a birthmark?
还是第三个乳头吗
Is that a third nipple?
天晓得
Who knows?
这种东西书上可找不着
You can't write this crap!
等等  等等  我再看看
Hold up, hold up, hold up. Let me see.
我明白了
I get it.
对  的确  再看就好多了
Yeah, I guess, on second look, it's better.
今天的第一首歌有些深沉
This, uh... first song goes pretty deep.
名叫  "老爹"
It's called "Daddy."
至少是首家庭歌曲
Uh... at least it's, uh, uh, a family song.
*老爹  你抛弃了我*
*Daddy! You abandoned me!*
*老爹  你把我变成瘾君子*
*Daddy! You sold drugs to me!*
*一天到晚狠揍我*
*Punches are not hugs to me!*
这不是"老妓女"那首歌
Eh. It's no "Elderly Prostitute."
鲍鲍  你不是跟他谈过了吗
Bobby, you said you talked to him.
谈过了吧  算是
Uh, I did, kinda.
但他把我们以前的违规记录都清零了
But then he wiped our record clean.
*老爹  你是我的仇敌*
*Daddy! You're my enemy!*
*你是我的仇敌  我的仇敌*
*You are my enemy! My enemy!*
*你是我的仇敌  我的仇敌  我的仇敌*
*You are my enemy! My enemy! My enemy!*
别  你闭嘴  这是我的独唱
No, don't. It's just me, just me, just me.
*我的仇敌*
*My enemy!*
对不起
Oh, sorry.
*就是你呀你*
*You, you, you!*
*娇小的脱衣舞娘爬上铜杆*
*The Itsy-Bitsy Stripper climbed up the brassy pole*
*她垂下双腿  紧紧裹住我的魂*
*Down came her legs and wrapped around my soul*
*你的欲望编织成了一张网*
*Weave your web of your sexy web*
*一张欲网牢牢绑住我*
*Weave your sexy web around me*
*编起欲网  邪恶的欲网*
*Weave your web, weave your naughty web*
*绑住我的身体  我漂亮的身体*
*Around my body, my beautiful body*
*我漂亮的双腿  我漂亮的躯体*
*My beautiful legs, my beautiful torso*
*一张欲网牢牢绑住我*
*Weave that web around me...*
沙滩上摆栅栏干嘛
Hurdles on a beach?
这些拖着一副皮囊的人又想搞什么花样
What are those silly little skin bags up to now?
等下  我来看看
Wait a second.
不了个是吧
This can't be.
各位  我劝你们
Uh, guys, you might want to buy seats now,
为明天的盛会提前买票
for tomorrow's event.
"裸运会"
"Nudecathlon."
听着像奥运会  只不过是全裸参赛
That sounds like decathlon, but nude.
他们年纪一大把还全裸着
They're naked and old
为拿金牌拼命呢
and they're bringing home the gold!
你去  跟他说
Go! You go talk to him!
好吧
All right.
汤米  我有事要跟你谈谈
Tommy, listen, there's something I need to talk to you about.
我在想  也许
I was thinking, maybe, um...
你可以休息休息  先别演了
you could take some time off from performing... uh, here.
啥  你什么意思啊  小鲍鲍
What? What, what are talking about, Bobby boy?
就是说
It's just that, um...
你唱得这么好
you know, you could be performing at...
去别处发展会更有前途
at way different places.
我是不是可以理解为
Huh, it's almost like you're saying
你不想我在店里唱歌了
you don't want me to play here anymore.
不不  不是
No. Not... No.
你  没完全明白我意思
You... took that the wrong way. Uh-huh.
-我的意思是  你很出色  -是么
- What I meant was... you're great. - Right.
我们的小庙容不下你这尊大佛
Um, but just not maybe for, for here.
我跟你说件有趣的事
I'll tell you what's funny,
你这番话
you know, that's what the manager
之前"手枪酒吧"的经理也说过
over at Pistol McSwish's said, too.
-是吗  -是  可以说一模一样
- Did he? - Yeah, kind of exactly.
不过挺遗憾的  那小子
And it's a shame about that guy... you know,
拜我所赐  关门大吉了
he got shut down by me.
你做了什么
What are you doing?
我本来不想说的  可是
You know, I hate to say this, but, you know,
你地板上都是老鼠屎啊  老兄
you got rat turds on your floor, man,
不好意思  通通要记录
and, yeah, I-I gotta write that up, unfortunately.
什么  汤米  你疯了吧
What? Tommy, that's crazy.
你兜里随时装着老鼠屎吗
You just carry around bags of rat turds in your pocket?
是吗  我不知道你在说什么
Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about.
看看  那边也有呢
Yeah, look over... see, I see some more right over here, see?
你连袋子都懒得掏了吗
You didn't even empty that one!
你想说刚有只老鼠跑过去
You're saying a rat just came in here
往地上拉了一袋子装好的屎吗
and tossed a bag of its poop on my floor?
对呀  就是这么回事
Yeah, that's a thing that happens.
其实要这事一笔勾销也容易
And look, you know, it can all go away.
就让我来个安可表演
Just let me do an encore,
然后每晚继续在这演出就行了
and then come back and play every night.
没门  汤米  就凭你那二流的摇滚
No, Tommy! You're not gonna hold us hostage
休想逼我们就范
with your crappy music and your threats!
二流
Crappy?!
马上滚出我的餐馆  汤米
So get out of my restaurant, Tommy!
好  想必你很清楚这意味着什么
Okay! Of course, you know what this means:
你被停业了  等进一步通知  兄弟
Until further notice, you are shut down, my man!
知道了  那你还不赶紧滚  兄弟
Fine! Why don't you get out, my man?!
求之不得  兄弟
Oh, gladly, my man!
告诉你吧  你的鱼泡眼真丑爆了
Oh, and guess what?! You do have bulging eyes!
真扫兴
And it is off-putting!
所以  进  进行得如何
So, uh... h-how did, uh, how'd it go?
好极了
Great.
通告  停业整顿
食品质检局发  请勿擅自揭下
未能通过检查  业主违反下列条例
警告 本店查证有老鼠屎
我们饿了 鲍鲍  开门
We're hungry, Bobby! Open up!
不行  泰迪  汤米勒令我停业
I can't, Teddy. Tommy closed us down.
我要是给你开门  我就要进监狱
If I serve you, I could go to jail.
我们愿意冒这个险
We're willing to take that chance!
如果汤米不让我们营业
If Tommy doesn't let us open,
要不了一周我们就会破产了
we'll be broke by next week!
我们得想个办法  鲍鲍
We gotta fix this, Bobby!
现在只有他能帮我们了
There's only one person who can help us now.
天哪
Oh, God.
别这么紧张  这是很自然的
Oh, don't be so nervous. It's natural.
这是什么状况
What's going on here, anyway?
裸体运动会  有意思
Naked field day! Fun!
他在那儿  真不敢相信
There he is. I can't believe
我要去抱光着屁股的雨果的大腿
I'm gonna grovel to a naked Hugo.
鲍勃  琳达  你们来得正好
Bob! Linda! You're just in time
这个裸体绳球比赛我就快获胜了
to see me excel at nude tetherball!
雨果  是这样  我来是请你帮忙的
Hugo, look, I've come to ask for your help.
那个接替你的人关了我们的餐厅
The guy who replaced you shut down the restaurant.
鲍勃  真遗憾
Oh, Bob, that's a pity.
不过我已经不关心卫生检查领域的事了
But the health-inspecting world doesn't interest me anymore.
拜托  那人就是个疯子  雨果
Come on. This guy's nuts, Hugo.
他居然自己搜集老鼠屎  你都不会那样
He, he planted rat poop. You wouldn't even do that.
听听你说的话  鲍勃
Listen to you, Bob!
全是你自己那点破事儿
It's all about things with you!
餐厅  老鼠屎  内衣裤
Restaurants! Rat feces! Underwear!
-我的天  -今天可是裸运会
- Oh, God. - Today is the Nudecathlon,
你要么脱光衣服加入我
so either you join me in nude brotherhood
要么就乖乖回你的"文明"国度去
or kindly return to your clothed country.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
-如  如果我加入呢  -多多益善啊
- What, what if I did join you? - The more the merrier.
可要是我参赛并且还赢了你呢
But what if I competed and beat you?
不可能
Uh, you won't.
如果我赢了呢  到时候你会帮我们吗
But if I did, would you help us out then?
-你是要跟我打赌吗  鲍勃  -是的
- Is this some kind of bet, Bob? - Yeah. It's a bet.
那要是我赢了呢
And what do, what do I get if I win?
你说了算
Well, what do you want? You have to cater
你要免费为裸运会的闭幕式提供饮食
the Nudecathlon closing ceremony for free.
如果这就是代价的话  我认了
If this is what it takes, this is what it takes.
鲍勃  你知道自己在做什么吧
Bob, you do realize what you're getting yourself into.
裸运会有27个项目
A nudecathlon has 27 events,
热身的木头人游戏可不算哦
not including warm-up freeze tag.
我退出
I quit.
别  鲍鲍  加油  你可以的
No, Bobby, come on! You can do it!
连本带利式  正序连赢  三连胜式
Parlays, exactas, trifectas!
均为赛马赌博方式
我们这儿全都接受  各位
We're taking all action, people!
露易丝  你得过来看看这个
Louise, you're gonna want to see this.
我们玩火上身
We played with fire,
现在报应来了  闪瞎了我的狗眼啊
and this is what we get... fire in our eyes!
考虑到老爸已经有三个孩子了
I think Dad looks pretty good,
这样的身材已经很不错了
considering he's had three kids.
老爸  别做那个动作
Hey, Dad, stop stretching like that!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
现在由齐克在这个阳光明媚的下午
Zeke here, calling the action for you
为您带来现场解说
on this sunny afternoon.
今天的赢家只有一个
There can only be one winner today,
"软塌塌的香肠"倒是不少
but many floppy wieners.
比赛开始了
And they're off!
肥佬暂时领先
Doughboy's out to an early lead!
冲啊  鲍鲍  冲啊
Go, Bobby, go!
*历史总是惊人的相似*
*History repeats itself*
*只要努力  就能成功*
*Try, and you'll succeed...*
你今天可有的受了  鲍勃
You've got a tough day ahead of you, Bob.
鲍勃：雨果  0:1
*你就能实现梦想*
*And you can have your dream*
*你是最棒的*
*You're the best around*
好像沙漏里往下流的沙子
Like sand through his hourglass!
*你是最棒的*
*You're the best around*
*你无人能敌*
*Nothing's ever gonna keep you down*
*你是最棒的*
*You're the best around...*
雨果
Hugo.
*你无人能敌*
*Nothing's ever gonna keep you down...*
鲍勃:雨果  1:3
拔河比赛大胖子赢了
Big fatty wins the tug!
小胖子这次不走运了
Bad luck, little fatty!
鲍勃:雨果  7:7
接下来是"两人三足两二货"项目
Three legs, four thighs and two ding-dongs.
满眼的小鸡鸡  真恶心
Now that's one nasty bucket of chicken!
*尽全力打败一切对手*
*Try your best to win them all*
*总有一天  时间会证明*
*And one day, time will tell*
*你是幸存者中的佼佼者*
*When you're the best that's standing there*
鲍勃:雨果  10:11
*你会坚持到最后*
*You'll reach the final bell*
*我是最棒的*
*I'm the best around*
*我无人能敌*
*Nothing's gonna ever keep me down*
鲍勃:雨果  13:13
*我是最棒的*
*I'm the best around...*
怎么样啊  鲍勃
How are we holding up, Bob?
很好  好极了
Fine! Just great!
我得承认
Well, I must say you've proven yourself
你是个不错的裸运会对手
a worthy naked adversary.
不过谁能赢到所有的弹珠还要看最后一搏
But this last event is for all the marbles.
marble有弹珠的意思  也用于形容长得又圆又肥的人
别跟我提弹珠
Don't say marbles.
请排好队  古典式摔跤比赛马上开始
Line up for Greco-Roman wrestling!
加油  鲍勃  你是我的光屁屁骑士
Go, Bobby! You're my big naked knight!
我快挂了
I'm dying.
男士们  请入场
Gentlemen, enter the ring.
为最棒的裸体而战
May the best nude win.
别抓那儿
Ah, not there.
我抓这儿
There you go.
-吃我这招  -放开我
- Take this one. - Let go!
扫腿  老爸  扫腿
Sweep the leg, Dad! Sweep the leg!
把他想成裸体的糖果盒  老爸
Treat him like a naked pinata, Dad!
把它劈开拿颗糖来吃
Break him open for some candy!
好了  鲍勃  是你发挥的时候了
Okay, Bob, time to do this!
今天你可别想  鲍勃
Not today, Bob!
小个像翻肉饼一样把胖大个摔了个狗吃屎
Oh! The little guy flips the fatty like a patty!
-分出胜负了  -不
- We've got a pin! - No!
太棒了  我赢了
Yes! I win!
你先是从我这儿抢走了琳达
You took Linda from me,
接着又成了我事业的绊脚石
you were the scourge of my professional life,
这次我终于赢了
but this time, I win!
你可以从我身上下来了  雨果
You can get off me now, Hugo!
永远别想
Never!
我赢了
I win!
-我们回家  琳  -好吧
- Let's go home, Lin. - All right.
我赢了  赢了  赢了
I win, win, win!
真激烈啊
Wow. That was rough.
光着身子被打败
Naked and defeated.
跟他来到这个世上时的状态一样
Just the way he entered this world.
鲍鲍  你裤子穿反了  宝贝儿
Bobby, you put your pants on backwards, honey.
不重要  一切都不重要了
Doesn't matter. None of it matters.
我们丢了餐厅  琳
We lost the restaurant, Lin.
蒂娜  我们也把裤子反着穿吧
Tina, let's put our pants on backwards, too.
为老爸
Let's do it for Dad!
我穿的是裙子  不过也好
I'm wearing a skirt, but okay.
雨果  你来这儿做什么
Hugo? What are you doing here?
你怎么又穿衣服了
And why are you wearing clothes?
还是那只是彩绘
Or is that just body paint?
今天在海滩你已经尝到了被我打败的滋味
Today, at the beach, you tasted my sweet victory,
不过后来我意识到  这还不够
but I realized something: It wasn't enough.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
关掉你店的人应该是我  是我
I want to shut you down... I do...
而不是某个二货  是我才对
not some dirty doody-dropper... me.
在那之前  你可以营业
Until then, you're open for business.
罗恩
Ron?
收到  兄弟
You got it, buddy.
太好了
All right!
谢谢你  雨果
Well, thanks, Hugo.
好了  各位  进来吧
All right, everyone! Load in!
-怎么回事  -闭幕式啊  鲍勃
- What's going on? - The closing ceremony, Bob.
你忘了吗  你要包办啊
Remember? You have to cater it.
尽情脱吧
Disrobe at will!
不用费心在座位上垫纸巾
Don't bother with courtesy tissues on the seats.
裸体进食  我喜欢
Gettin' nude for food! I love it!
拿好你的汉堡  我说得对不
Hold the buns. Am I right?!
buns可指面包  也有屁股的意思
最好先把桌子下面的口香糖清理了
Well, better clean up the gum under the tables.
我现在就去
I'll get to it.
蒂娜  别动  我恨你  雨果
Tina, no. I hate you, Hugo.
等等  汤米・贾龙达去哪儿了
Wait... what about Tommy Jaronda?
你们好  吉米・派丝多的客人们
How we doin', Jimmy Pesto's?
*我是个有绝技的坏男人*
*I'm a bad man with a master plan*
*姑娘们都叫我特克斯*
*And the ladies call me Tex*
*她们都心知肚明*
*And the one thing all the ladies know is*
*我是擅长做爱*
*I'm good at having*
*做爱爱爱爱爱*
*sex-sex-sex-sex-sex*
*我是做爱高手  我是做爱高手*
*I'm good at sex, I'm good at sex*
*我是做爱的高高高高手*
*I'm very, very, very, very good at sex*
*我擅长  你也擅长*
*I am good, you are good, too*
*你的技术日渐长进*
*You're learning, little by little*
*我手把手指导你*
*I'm guiding you with my hand and my arms*
*我是做爱高手  你进步迅猛*
*I'm good at sex, you're learning quick...*